# Time Lost-A Computer Adventure (TI-99/4a)

Included is a pdf scan of the original book, Time Lost: A Computer Adventure (TI-99/4a) 
Thanks to the Internet Archive at https://archive.org/details/tibook_ti994a-timelost/page/n25/mode/1up?view=theater
for making it available.

As I get the source code entered, I will add it.

Current List:
Battle at Stonehenge
Attack of the Slime Creatures

